

# **NGUYEN VAN A**

### **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and which toil and pain can procure him s of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

### **EDUCATION**



### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. ur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore e administration

₩ Sep 2007 - Present

### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

### **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

# **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult ế kỉ, mà khi được áp dụng vào tin học vă and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

### Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and
- Assist to onorum et Malorum goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

# **ACTIVITIES**



### **CVPRO JSC**

#### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer M" Original Latin text: "At vero eos et accusamus et iusto' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

# **CERTIFICATIONS**



**TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO** 2004

# **HONORS & AWARDS**



**TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO** 

2013 - 2014

# **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US pleasure. To take a trivial example, which of us ever undertakes laborious physic

### **REFERENCES**



### **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

**01234567890** mbinhnv@topcv.com

# **SKILLS**



Words Photoshop Excel **English** Power Point • **Japanese** 

# **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt C. This book is a treatise on the theory of and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities